{\an2\candH00F5F8
Subtitle and video transcript from the same place
The only website in Sri Lanka that offers
(www.PirateLk.Com)
See where this love story of two hearts has taken us..
Our meeting in these lines..
Written even before birth..
<font color="
Don't stop today..
Promise me not to break up now..
That you won't give up being with me..
Own you today.. or die..
Don't break this dream..
Ask my dear..
<font color="
I am yours..
Only yours..
Bhool Bhulaiyaa 3
(Maze 3)
After 200 years..
P
Para
<font color="
Circ
Computer
Computer a
Computer Horn
Computer no
Computer notation
Computer notation data
Computer notation teeth
<font color="
Computer notation data
Computer notation data p
Output computer notation data
Computer notation data copy
Computer notation data copy no
<font color="
Computer notation data copy creation
Computer notation data copy design
Computer notation data copy creation p
<font color="
Creation of computer notation data copy Chap
Computer notation data copy creation Par
Computer notation data copy creation accompanying
Computer notation data copy creation converter
Computer notation data copy design translation
Computer notation data copy creation and translation
<font color="
Computer notation data copy design conversion
Computer notation data copy creation and conversion
Computer notation data copy design conversion and etc
Computer notation data copy creation conversion and sub
<font color="
Computer notation data copy creation, translation and interpretation
Computer notation data copy creation, translation and subtitling
Computer notation data copy creation translation and subtitling
<font color="
Computer notation data copy creation, translation and subtitling c
Computer notation data copy creation, translation and subtitling
Computer notation data copy creation about translation and subtitling
<font color="
Computer notation data copy creation converted and subtitled
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
<font color="
e
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
eat
Idu
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
<font color="
before
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
After that
<font color="
After
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
because
Still still
<font color="
Next to Nisal
Computer-coded data copy creation, translation and subtitling
Next is Nisal
100th subtitle
Rooh Baba
Please
- Baba, save our child
Baba this soul..
- Calm down
This is not your son's business
That demon spirit
This is a very dangerous ghost.
I am with a client now.. I will call you later
god
let's go
What kind of thief did you catch?
Not everyone will be possessed by demons just because they wear black clothes
So pull a white sherwani to catch you?
Pinto
Baba took it away
Thief.. did you sneak into his body?
What to do now Baba?
You removed that batali from his body
Now you have to sneak somewhere, don't you?
I have been removed eight times before.. I don't know where to sneak in
Drop them
How about your piece.. still under the sacred fig tree
That's how love happens, right?
Oh Baba, if you are..
- Baba is our son
sorry sorry
Pintu son.. leave
No, Baba.. I will not leave, Baba
A very comfortable body.. I will not come out Baba
Is that so.. very stubborn
Get out now
- No
I will not leave Baba
I won't quit..
- Pinto
Oh my son is hurt
These are not bullets
Pure wine
Pinto.. Pinto
- Baba.. Baba
mother
father
my child
- My son got better
My son got well
- Is this urine?
No, son.. Please
- Who are you brother?
This is Rooh Baba.. He is the one who saved your life
Thank you Baba.. Thank you
I don't know if you weren't there..
What will happen?
When mom and dad come back, my..
Loses life
At such a time only one person can save
Rooh Baba
Don't worry
Remember a name
Pinto
Pinto..
The world is stupid..
Those who are afraid of demons
You want to take advantage of them
Nano.. what's on your neck?
This is the anniversary gift
- This is direct death, bye.. This is also cursed
Cursed too
This is also a cursed person
If something goes wrong, blame it on the demons
Who they are come and speak for themselves
Rooh Baba.. Rooh Baba
Rooh baba..
Ruh baba..my wife is me with my queen..
Caught with my cheating wife
Is he a bad man?
Yes Baba
- Irishness
Do you know Bengali?
- I am Malayadi
Not Bangadi.. I don't know
I don't know.. I have to learn
A little bit
my sister
i love you
- Dad.. Dad
my sister..
Baba ji what happened to my man?
- This is not your man.. Ghosh Babu
What Ghosh Babu?
Two years ago, he became paralyzed and died after drinking alcohol
Since then, his soul has been inside him
Dad.. Dad
- Bang.. Good, good, because how well you do is the top
Oh father father.. that means father
Dad.. Dad
- Oh father.. good
Baba ji save me
I will save you, you will save me.. But Ghosh Babu's soul was very much addicted to lust
So whenever his soul enters your husband..
They will try to catch your brother who is working for you
my sister..
- Look for it
Narayana.. Rama Krishna Rama
What sin did I commit?
- Don't think.. Don't think
Hey little one.. It's good, isn't your father?
- Good, good, good
Do you know what is the worst case of demons?
Leave a common man.. a king will not leave even a Maharaj
Wow.. Great splendor, great light, great appearance, great wealth
When you see the face, you can know that the king is the king
Not a king now
Raja is our cousin
That is why I thought that this light and this glory has dimmed
Say the name
My brother-in-law's daughter is Raja Kumari Meera
Last year we left everyone behind and left the world
wow
I said how
How did you go?
A road accident
Since then, his soul feels like he is wandering
Talk to him once
I can feel it
His soul is somewhere here..
Raja Kumari Meera
Talk to me.. where are you?
Looks like he's embarrassed
Where the hell is the switchboard?
Meeroo
Talk to me children.. Come here
This... this
Here it is
Awa.. Where is Baba.. Meeru?
hey
Tilloo
That same girl.. Oh my God, how quickly you died.. What a waste
I'm sorry Meeroo.. Ram Ram
He says.. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Nothing special.. you seem busy.. see you later
Talked to me
Saying now
A vampire
Bay.. Save
save me
I mean, uncle.. he is the number one cheater
completely
are you alive
- Yes.. but you are dead
uncle
A vampire
Aren't you ashamed?
Cheating on such a small person?
Do you have.. are you cheating the whole world?
what do you want
- Even knowing that you are the number one cheater..
We want to use your Baba service
And for that you have to go to our kingdom Raktaghat
Is my brain damaged, should I go to Raktaghat with you?
I'm not going anywhere
- Should I upload this first on Instagram or YouTube?
Don't worry
If you do our work, we will give you one crore rupees
A crore?
What time is the flight?
If you are done waiting, look elsewhere
No, I wasn't waiting
I'm just thinking.. if you are from a royal family..
Then why go by this train?
- We are not like other kings and queens
We do not think of the difference between our own sacrifices
Living simply..thinking big
- Great
Tell me one more thing.. even though you know I am number one..
The number one liar..
Then why are you taking me?
You will know when you go further
wow
Raktghat
Look at that
Does everyone in this village have any disease?
Why was everyone staring at me?
- Will know
Let's go.. His Majesty is waiting for you
yes come
- Oh, not there
His Majesty is not in the palace
then?
Clay bungalow?
- What to say..
There is a demon in our palace
A demon?
- Manjulika.. so no one is there for fear
So the whole family had to move to the clay bungalow
At one time, thousands of our cows were tied here..thousands
Now there is only one left.. Shaiga
Is this Shaiga?
Don't say that
Uncle.. It's time to take milk from him
Das
- Yes
Your cow does not give milk.. it drinks
Yes, he is weak and helpless
- Weak?
Whose stomach is itchy?
What is going on here?
Take it here sister.. Keep it for tomorrow
For tomorrow?
Oh, now you can drag on for another week
You do something
keep mine
Oh, great
This will be good for the whole year
- Yes
asking
How did you build such a figure even though you are so poor?
Hey Paharaya.. talk with kindness..
We are princes of a royal family.. princes
- Oh bye
Say anything you want in front of me.. but don't tell this prince story
(referring to the film Shehzada)
Attention..Accept.. The King of Raktghat
Getting comfortable..
May His Majesty win
- Hey, hey
Me and His Majesty
This is our bodyguard.. Pholad Singh
This.. Pholad Singh?
He has been protecting us since the time of our grandfather
Now he is getting old, so we have to take good care of him
- What kind of state is this?
The cow has to be milked... it has to be protected
we
I have been waiting for you for a long time
Did you hear?
You can talk to demons.. do it
- Can do
Bhojana is waiting for you.. Come
I felt very hungry, King
royal meals
Pholad Singh
my bread
I will protect you
Promised
If this bread is poisoned like that, you will die
shut up
I'm starving to death
God.. If you don't beg like this, Somalia wouldn't even exist
Raja Kumari's mother..
Raja Kumari
come here
Please take some and eat this too
What?
You don't have a penny
How can you give me a crore?
You will get the answer in the evening
Pranam
Namaste Pranam G
This Rajapurohita G
Namaste Rajapurohita G
I have been waiting for you since my previous self
But your story was written for my destiny
what are you doing bro
I am thankful
oh what's going on
- Shut up
come on
I will not come
- Let's shut up
money
let's go
Did you see it?
Where are you.. Oh, are you going to leave anyone alone?
This is not yours, this is a picture of the prince
Rajakumara Devendranath's house
You are his next birth
After birth?
To understand that story, you have to know the history of this state
History
Like Rajakumara Devendranath's..
Sister Manjulika's..
Raja Kumari Manjulika is the only daughter of Maharaja
An expert in the art of drama.. and the best on the battlefield
No one in the entire state had a goal like him
He knew that he would find the throne of the Maharaja in the future
Later, the Maharaja had a son from one of his maidservants
Devendranath
Deboo..Deboo
His Majesty began to show him his kindness
take care
Hane is my little brother
Why are you crying on my sister's lap?
my little brother
Even so, his faith was not broken
Because Devendranath's body had the blood of one hundred slaves
But when the time comes
Then the Maharaja handed over his crown to Devendranath
And that night, Manjulika killed her brother very cruelly
What is the punishment to be given to him?
Death penalty
This is where he was burned
Everyone thought this was the end of the story
But even death could not stop Manjulika
He came back to take his revenge
Stop the spirit of Manjulika, my ancestors with one great puja
Pure oil was taken
And he was locked behind that door forever
This Bhairav ​​Kavach will be able to stop Manjulika
He cannot be destroyed
And according to future astrologers..
Someone will be reborn as a royal family to end Manjulika
And he comes and opens this door on Durghashtmi day
This kingdom has been waiting for you since the last 200 years
me
- Yes
Tomorrow is the first day of Durga Puja
Just like Madhurwale finished Maishasur..
you too
Manjulika finishes
On a Durgashtami day
Don't even think of going near this gate before that
Oh, I won't even think about that.
- Why is Pandit ji talking about going near Manjulika?
Because you are not an ordinary person
- Then what am I?
You are the prince of this kingdom
Prince
Prince.. Prince?
You were born to do this
What has to be done?
End of Manjulika
Get to know yourself
There is no need to worry about anyone here when you are there, Yuvarajuni
yes
No need to worry
I am the prince
royal
I have blue blood
From my childhood, I knew that there was something special in me.. I was not an ordinary person
But fate crept in
Today this life is passing in the middle.. Chi
Poor people
This is the lack of muscle
I feel right now
As soon as I said it, another girl was crying
what are you doing
- Shut up maid
the maid?
- Yes, and remember
This palace is mine
Not yours
- Hello
All these demonic reincarnations are nonsense.. they are all stupid things.. get it?
Does that mean?
Don't you believe these things?
Definitely.. I don't believe it
If father had not promised, I would have gone and opened Manjulika's door for a long time.
But it doesn't matter
Now I need this blind faith
You open that door on Durgashtami day
Then this palace
It will sell for at least 1000 crores
1000 crores?
Don't worry.. you will get your 1 crore
1 crore?
greedy woman
Hello.. Let's go
Because of your self-confidence, the whole family wants to move to the palace
We should not be here now
How much time is left for Durgashtami?
father
There is something else that scares me too
what
- Higanakama.. Our whole life was spent in that clay bungalow..
And why are you scared?
Now the prince is with us
Even so, if you have any problem, there is Folard Singh to protect you?
Where is Pholad Singh?
brother in law
Look what I brought
This.. here
- Hey idiot
How much blood was taken and sold?
Oh, the blood was not sold.. Donations were made. Oh, they were donated
Donated?
- When the villagers found out..
The prince has come with us to the palace.. People started donating again
Great.. Does that mean you will always have food to eat at home?
- Of course
Then we don't have to go to temples to pick up sandals?
- No
Then we don't have to pick toffees from the trash cans for sweets?
very good
Now, with this money, let's make some new additions to the palace
Let's go.. We also have to go to the God Mandir
May the royal prince win
On the occasion of Durga Puja..
Every year
The whole village has burnt Manjulika's pyre
But this time set it on fire.. themselves
The prince has come here
Long live the royal prince!
- King Digvijaya
Who is there?
hands down
What is a prince, how is a prince, where is a prince?
This is not any prince
Leave the prince
Not even the royal prince's "foot".
- Where did the letter "pa" come from when you say prince?
"Pa" comes from "pa"
(initial letter)
This is a thief... a fraud
a liar
This is coming
Memory.. come once
This is a liar
Come once.. Came
- This is a liar
My coronation
It happened in this house
the hand
I went horse riding.. then that field was outside
Kook fought
the hook
- Cockfighting
Oh Lantoo, Puntoo and Tuntuny
What lantu.. what puntu what tuntuni?
I am a small scholar.. a big scholar.. a scholar
So this soul is crazy?
In the past, you are Lantu, you are Puntu, then you are Tuntuni
You massaged my hand.. your leg.. then you
Pawan Saluwa
Lies. Only lies.. I'm massaging your legs, not your hands
What did you say?
- Prove that he is a liar
Well, let's say.. Then I am not your leg.. I am massaging your hand
Did you see? Did you see? The memory comes back a little
You tighten your knees a little more
Get full memory back..
Because it can be of little use to our people
What is good for us?
- How is that?
In my departed soul, I handed over my treasure to these three people for my people
treasure
- Treasure?
At least 30000 gold coins in that treasure..
There were diamonds, pearls, and all kinds of jewels
Before my people get my treasure..
These three stole the treasure
Then hid.. and then..
disappeared
- Disappeared?
Now if their memory comes back..
Then we will know where these three have hidden the treasure.
Where is our treasure hidden?
Where is the treasure?
Whose treasure and where is the treasure? This is all a conspiracy
Please stop, stop
Why are you beating my family members like dogs?
No one's memory of being hit like that will come back
I read somewhere.. because I read a lot
If you do the things of the past soul again in this soul..
Then people's memory can come back
Just like my Ava.. right now
Yes, that's exactly right.. isn't it, uncle?
- 200% right.. right brother?
yes good
- Yes, fine
Then the story became solid.. Now you three are sitting in my palace and serving me
We are all together squeezing your neck
Oh, if you don't go, how can we find the treasure?
Excuse me.. you?
Mallika.. came from crown heritage restoration..
Yes.. this company restores old properties
I also called further
But wasn't Kaushik ji supposed to come instead of you?
He went on a long vacation
For a long vacation.. I talked to him yesterday.. Wait a second
Not getting it
- He said.. he went on a long vacation
It's okay
He will replace him
welcome
- Come on
So you are the reincarnation of the prince?
yes
Did you remember anything about anyone.. Your father, His Majesty.. The rest of the relatives
Or your sister Manjulika
No, it hasn't come yet
will come
- Yes.. It's coming
Come, let me show you to your room
survived
A cool place
is it true
Meera.. don't jump again
There is a staircase to go down in the back
I won't let you jump.. I won't let you jump..
- Move on.. Leave
what are you doing
Looking for excuses to catch up?
I thought you'd bounce back like last night
Last night.. Where did I go?
in my dream
So now you're dreaming of me dying, aren't you?
Whose bus is going in your dreams?
If my bus goes in my dreams..
You can't even imagine how you dream about yourself
Are you looking for excuses to touch me?
give up
no no
survived
You are a very big boy
a coward
- Crazy
crazy
Victory to the revolution.. Victory to the revolution..
Our employer is a crook
You are stupid
what are you saying
What's going on?
Excuse me for getting the memory back
Have you made a point and made us your servants?
Then you told us to do all the work
We will not do this work from now on
And the food is not prepared in any way
You alone are evil
Your work is done
My hands like flowers have disappeared
So it should have been said earlier
I will find some other way to get your memory back
So find another one
Will you find a Hunter?
- Hunter said?
A whip.. the whip is inside..
Why a whip?
- When you make those mistakes in the departed soul..
Then they whipped your face
Whips to the face?
- When two hundred or three hundred whips hit
The memory will return automatically
Two hundred and fifty finished
are you ok
I'm fine.. Are you waiting for it to fly?
listen listen..
- Dada Muni
Dada Bro
What do you like to eat?
Palappanir
Or do you like paneer?
- Make both
Kala will tell you what you like
Well, hurry up and start working
didn't you sleep
Hey, no, no
The curse of these things has come to me
He likes weapons very much
No one in the entire state had a goal like his
Even with his eyes closed, he never lost sight of his goal
Isn't it?
What are you saying lady.. do you think you are Manjulika?
Oh lady, it is not possible for everyone to achieve a goal like his
you sleep
hello
Rooh Baba is speaking
Welcome to our program
Come let's talk
Our next conversation
what is your name
Yes.. Manjulika
Who do you want to message?
to my brother
My treasure..my dear brother
You came back
But you will not be saved
I am out
And you are listening
Your death is written in this soul and my hand
Just like I died now you will die
You will have to work hard
It will take a lot of drilling
Oh, oh, oh
Black cat.. go away
Black cat.. Run away.. Get out of here
A fire broke out
- Where did it go now?
- Oh, there's a fire
A fire has started..come quickly come quickly
A fire broke out
How did this painting spontaneously combust?
The thing to think about is why did this painting catch fire?
This is done by Manjulika
yes..
- He had an enmity with this prince
Enmity
- I said infinite
We should not have stayed here
oh oh oh
Is it burnt? It's very sad
You're not afraid of the painting, it's like you were on fire
It's just a picture
Damn.. I'm not lifting
Oh Tilloo
Why are you not answering my calls?
Then why change this ringtone?
Arahe threatens Manjulika on the radio
Then the picture of Rajakumara Devendranath caught fire by itself
That means me
what
I had a very big belly
I'm royal.. you don't know
I am leaving this maze.. you too are going.. time and time again
- Hello hello
Don't even think of going back.. I ran away from there too..
ran away.. why?
Oh, there are clients who have caught us..
He is brother of ACP Rathore..
- Which ACP Rathore?
Oh, what do I know?
Isn't ACP enough?
I heard that it is very dangerous
Oh boy.. ACP Rathore on one side
And on the other hand, Manjulika.. what am I doing?
Let's do something.. Let's go somewhere and hide.. Let's think later
But before that, delete that ghost video of yours from that Bhutini's phone
good
Then what did you say about that manjulika.. who is she?
Oh, he is a number one monster
A witch, a ghost, a rassi
He comes as soon as he sees blood
Hey Rasgullah
Down time.. Down time
is coming
What?
Will you do something for me?
- Why?
ask
I want your sister's phone
But he can't know.. Take it, son
the fruit
I have honest blood
It is full of loyalty
you want
Should I cheat on my sister?
20 will be given
ok
Oh, not blood.. there was chutney.. chutney
- Are you sure?
Have you brought it, son.. Great
The password?
- Another Rs.20 goes
rob me
I knew you would definitely try to steal my phone
Fortunately, I had left a password
don't you like me
what
Not at all
why
Because what you see is one and another
It's hard to understand you
But I understand you very well
Hello.. Don't try to understand too much
Just understand this, as long as this video of yours is on my phone..
Don't even think about leaving here
In any case, Ruh Baba's appearance makes me look like a bastard
right?
I don't know about the video
But as long as you have my photos on your phone..
I'm not going anywhere
Nobody came..ever after you..
The city of this heart.. is empty..
Your dreams.. in those moments..
<font color="
Goed without fruit.. without goal.. without purpose..
My love for you increased a little..
What ever happened to you..
<font color="
Some love or some playful enjoyment of affection..
This soul is yours..
Your rights have never been claimed..
I will not fight with loneliness.. I will not fight with memories..
She who has become a shadow.. She is far from me even when I am close..
<font color="
My love for you increased a little..
Who is the girl in this picture?
Madhulika Devi
- Manjulica
Wife of Rajakumara Devendranath
Oh my wife
Not very hot please..
But her lips suit you very well
You're not like that, are you?
- Want to talk nonsense all the time?
Oh, you said it's hot.. I didn't catch it.. Please listen
I don't want to hear anything.. You go
Oh, where are you going.. Oh, Manjulika's room
This is there
this..
- Bhairav ​​Kavach
should have gone
Said to go
You will not be saved
Let go of me
what are you doing
let me go
Where are you taking...Manjulika is there
should have gone
They asked you to go.. Did you bring someone else with you?
going to go
Oh, why don't you go?
Oh my throat hurts.. Please go away
You beat me.. my treasure
my treasure you
Oh, he is not alone.. we are there too
My sister-in-law was killed..
- Are the three of you scary from the beginning?
Oh scary means we were scared too
After spending such a pleasant time.. you have come to the middle
Stupid thieves
Since when do these?
- I have to tell the truth
When did your mother die?
- Mine?
Two years ago
two years
- Two years
Sister.. We really came here from a long way..
The color changed after seeing the weather
Of course
Two years ago we came in our Rolls Royce..
In a Rolls Royce?
- Yes, we have two sisters
One is Rolls.. Another is Royce
There was a problem where we were sitting
So while leaving, got caught in the storm
He crept inside the palace to escape the storm
oh god
- What did you see?
This is Manjulika's palace
- Who is Manjulika?
The most famous ghost in this village
I am yours
shut up
What if those ghouls come and catch you?
Been with you for 35 years
Now what will that ghoul do to me?
Whatever else you do..
feel happy
But how did the lock break?
- The other incident lock
Rajapurohita's ancestors put a big lock on the door
It may rust over time and break on its own
And Manjulika?
- When we get inside..
Manjulika was not there then
Shah Jahan built the Taj Mahal for Mumtaz
Our Manjulika is for us..
Home sweet home
(beautiful house)
Keep fearing Manjulika
I put on a bigger lock than myself
Because no beggar like us..
Come here to get lost
Then you came to set fire to our happiness
If you open the room on Durshatmi day, our truth will be revealed
God.. How many games did you play to kick him out?
Just like Albert Hitchcock.
Scare him like that
got caught
The robber got scared and ran away
Are you scared?
- Yes.. The thief was afraid
Rooh Baba
I will take your soul out today
But you were a great man
The other one slapped me
Hey little sister
How did you know we scared you too?
Because I know you are not Manjulika
Akkanam was taken away
Well then.. The whole story was told and understood
Now it's time for us to sleep
You guys leave our house
Good night
Good night's little ones
Thieves
You scare me by wearing a cloth and sitting in the dark
Go now and tell your father about these people..
- Where are you going?
Why are you trying to screw up my million? You love me, don't you?
Let's tell this to father, uncle and the whole village.. tomorrow
But for my style
Mallika G.. You solved all our problems by revealing the truth of these people
I can do that much for you
You are like my little brother.
Then you do one more favor
- What?
Some time tomorrow
to you
Can it be Manjulika?
i am
Manjulica?
what happened
- Nothing
will be
thank you
Villagers
I thought a lot about waiting for Durgashtmi to open the door
But you have been waiting for 200 years
So why waste time?
That's why this door is open today..
I always close Manjulika's story
Raja Purohita said clearly
- Calm down
I know this work is very difficult
So help me in this work..
Village Maha..
The three Pandits
A round of applause
- Come on Pandit G.. What's wrong with no sound?
Pranaam.. Pranaam
Please welcome
Thank you..have some respect
- Not there
Big pundit till I do the pooja part..
Take a walk in the glowing stone fireplaces
- Good.. I will
Then the little Pandit too
Sit on the plate and pay attention
Then you are Pandita.. Spin around on the floor
Why did you make me do this?
- I don't
I won't do it
- Don't you?
You liars
Tell everyone your real image?
Are you going to destroy us?
For little pundits.. for big pundits.. for pundits
win
Go.. Go to start
Go straight
Go.. roll over
Fire.. to the skin
hurry up
Hey, it's not a game, it's a sacrifice
Light the Havan.. Havan
- Will you find a lighter?
Oh, is there anyone.. someone who smokes beedi cigarettes.. is there a lighter?
Burning fire
Light these up
This thief is making a noise
enough
Manjulica
Now your game is over
stops
enough
Ahead is dangerous
Manju
I am coming to you
Actin should be kept properly
Ok then.. Action
Manjulika comes out
How long have you been hiding behind the door?
Speak Bengali?
Did you lose the sound, Manju? Were you scared?
do you scare me
You don't know the fire inside me
I will burn you and the whole family with that fire
When your body is set on fire..
the body?
When taken from your bones..
That's when I find peace
Debu will finish you off
It's completely undone
None of you will be left behind
No one will be left behind..
Manjulika jumped
That woman was kicked out
To the prince
- Good luck
great
I said
Do not open this gate before Durgashtmi day
Look, Raja Purohita.. I respect you a lot
So nothing is hidden from you
The real story is that Manjulika's story is false
All the pandits of that village get together and make a Nadagam
The door was open
That means
Manjulika had already come out
He is waiting for someone
who
Maybe yours
I feel Manjulika is somewhere
And they set their next trap
what happened
It seems to be some sort of secret passage
Let's see.. what is the hidden secret
great
When one door opened, another closed
This castle of yours feels more extreme than a maze
Raja Purohita.. What are these things?
Now there is no answer for me
For that I built the gate of the Maharaja..
You have to go to that settlement.. the history of the entire kingdom is hidden
The answer will be found there.. but pay attention to one thing
Don't even think of opening this door until Durgashtmi
will go
Tell me.. welcome
Called the entire market to sell the palace
Then this second door came
Destroys
yes
But there is no way to open the door
His high priest said no
Let's hurry Tillu.. I have to catch the Hawada Express at 10.. Yaman son.
But why are you going back?
I can't stay in the dark now
In the dark?
- This one is burning now
Cut later
Can't pay the bill
When I found out about the second door..
No one will give gifts
And when the gift givers come back to ask for their money..
How do you pay, poor people?
After selling the blood, all the blood of my uncle is gone
Oh, but he is the one who gives blood
How do you give?
Look how much blood is left with the king
Oh, what a king, what kind of a king.. He has become a crook even more than us
With a sense.. Nadichcha Eko
He is weaker than before
He might have gone back to the clay bungalow and had some snacks
He may be using the toothpaste we gave him for 5 years.. but don't forget this
The king is the king
How much do you respect me?
Then why not help?
- The king is helping
You don't know our Ruh Baba's anger
- Anger?
What do you want to say now, Mr. King?
When going through a graveyard, big, big ghosts, ghosts, ghosts..
Take the legs back and go back
After going to 15 villages, the vampires tell their children to sleep.
Sleep little ghost.. or Ruh Baba will come
But there is no way for me to open the second door.. because the Raja Purohita said no
Alas, Raja Purohita did not even know about the second door
You can't live poor now
You open the door... let's take care of something else
As per your command, King
Tellu.. tell Meera and uncle
- Okay
did you see
I said
nothing
What have you done?
- The door is open, what else are you doing?
what are you doing
a disaster
there
I got to know something that no one else knew
Not one for His Majesty
Had two daughters
Rajakumari Anjulika
And Rajakumari Manjulika
Little sister is a storm
Then the big sister
a fire
If you know the details from one of them, you can dismiss it
Then the other person's
Still don't know
After opening this door, one thing can be said for sure
Now the beginning of destruction
certain
200 years ago
You are all welcome to the palace of Maharaja Suprabud of Raktghat
Today, a magnificent art exhibition will be presented in the King's palace
Rajakumari Manjulika and Rajakumari Anjulika
Without you, my heart is a wasteland..
I am like dry sand.. You are moisture..
From the art of silence..your voice comes..
<font color="
What is my life?
It is on you..
Even if I want.. I can't quench this lifelong desire..
Soduraneni..
Ask my dear..
The melody of my love..
<font color="
My desires are..
flows through the atmosphere..
Alive..
Even after destruction..
Ask my dear..
The melody of my love..
<font color="
flows through the atmosphere..
Alive..
Even after destruction..
I am yours..
Only yours..
Excellent..excellent
Happy with your dance..
I am going to give you both a surprise
I declare..
On the day of Durghashtami Puja, I am my royal throne
Handing over to the new prince
May the King win.. May the King win
That prince is.. your beloved
my son
Rajakumara Devendranath
May the King win.. May the King win
the present
Two doors were found.. Two of them left early.. Then these two sat and watched TV
baby
Look behind
were you scared
did you come
You are the lady of Maharaj Mandira in Surigarh
The one who wants to take our palace
I was very anxious to meet you
Restless?
- Just wanted to say thank you
thank you
to me
- Yes
If you don't open that door..
Then I will never be able to come
Does that mean?
- That means you opened the door
Manjulika jumped
That is why I was able to come here to buy the palace
I heard the other..
You can talk to demons
yes..
- That means when a demon appears in front of you
Will you catch him?
Yes.. definitely
- Delicious
Very tasty
Mrs. Mandira.. we have prepared a special room for you
Everything is ready
yes
- Can I stay in Manjulika's room?
why
- Just
The one in that room..
A demon had been locked up for so many years
The fun of being there will be different
right?
Yes, we have no problem
From here you are directly..
- know
He knows.. How does he know?
What will happen to Amma?
what is this
Look, he came
This is what could have happened
This is the first symbol
I said
Don't open that door
- Speak slowly, High Priest
People are coming to take the palace
If someone hears something, that's it..
Everything is destroyed
Then for today.. have mercy
Only one person can help you
who
That's not me
This one
What kind of buffalo is this?
what cow
- A buffalo
Why do you always put me first?
How do I kill him?
That's how you kill him.. Like
Manjulika as an end to the departed soul
Ginitiala.. This time we have to burn his soul and not his body
The knowledge of our sciences..
By making a weapon.. I make my ancestors and do the magic again
Then pure oil comes out from the burning fire
They are written
The last chapter of Manjulika's story
But until then, stay safe
because to me
I feel that he has come out
hey hey
His look
You all have it
This is the most beautiful place in our village
This place you see is the oldest house
let's go
- I'm not going to the mansion
why
I don't believe in God
Mandira is called Mandira in your name
Let's think of it as a tourist station.. Come on
- I said that I will not go to the mansion
I'm sorry.. I'm Nasik
Shall we go somewhere else?
Sure.. let's go
Namaskar
You all helped us a lot during our difficult time
We were taken care of.. today when we have a good time
How can we forget you?
So that's why today..
A feast from our side for the whole village
enjoy
Grandfather
Money is so little
Then you will donate.. Where did you get so many chickens?
shut up
Not chickens
crow
- Crow?
How many crows died last night?
They are entertained
- A crow treat?
shut up
Please, little sister, get a doll
Mallika Nona.. Mandira Nona
Nice to meet you
- Me too
come on
Nice to meet you
Same to me.. Come on
My dear.. My dear..
Look into my eyes and say what is in your heart..
<font color="
Live for you and die for your name..
Every breath is heavy with your name..
My dear, understand.. the heart says
<font color="
I will live and die in your arms.. with your love
My dear.. My dear..
Look into my eyes and say what is in your heart..
<font color="
I played with all these games of love..
Even if I give my heart, I will spend these nights alone..
You seem confused to me..
Otherwise I will solve the puzzles one by one..
My dear, please understand.. I am scared..
<font color="
My dear, understand.. I am yours..
Live in your dreams and die in your love
My.. My..
My dear.. My dear..
Look into my eyes and say what is in your heart..
<font color="
Hold with your hands.. Don't let go anywhere..
Party.. What is a party for, my lord?
You solved all the problems in our palace
thank you
Grab this quick
And go
go?
- Oh, there is the Howda Express at 10.. it will be late
Pack things.. be angry
Savitri
Honoring you with marbles..
Making a very large sculpture
Talking to aliens?
No.. with mother
Emotional
I'm not with him
what
What nonsense?
Are you talking to me like that now?
your heart
Injured
hey
Because your love is dead like mine?
King.. I forgot to tell you something
Not only can I talk to the soul
Spirits come and lodge inside me
Don't jump in and talk
Aunty Ji I am just..
- Shut up
I am talking to my husband
Don't get in the middle of it
Do you take your medicine every day?
Savitri
Yes Savitri
- Mom?
alive
what did you say
Making a marble sculpture of me?
Because the whole life of keeping me as a fake woman is over
Savitri
- Drop it
I don't want any sculpture
I just want a boy
a boy
- A boy?
For my daughter
Every mother has a dream
His daughter will one day be someone else's
The other I found the boy
who
how is he
mother
what are you doing
Don't you like him?
- Would like to
But..
- Then let me talk to my husband
I have seen this boy from the inside
- From the inside?
I am inside him
A diamond alone
Timu
- Timer
Mother.. If only you had asked Meera once
Well said.. Meera
To tell you the truth.. you love him, don't you?
Are you getting married?
yes mom
Getting married
ok
Get ready for the wedding soon
Thirty two inside..
- Hey, stop
sister
is the boy ok
What can I say sister.. great choice
good good
- Come on
Oh.. haven't you cleaned the room yet?
Hurry up, the buyers will come
- Calm down... we cleaned everything
Everything is clean
Hey clean up and show madam what you found
Idiots.. Why are you showing what was stolen?
I showed that this was stolen
good good
- Show the main thing
That means content
- As much as I know English
According to that.. Rajakumari Manjulika has written
Open it
Now Manjulika's secret is revealed
oh oh oh
Sorry sorry fell by mistake.. something important?
The paint fell
You roll like I lost someone's life?
Where did you bring me?
- In this room, all the royal clothes are kept
You pull Devendranath's sherwari
I am from Moreia
nonsense
good
But it's ridiculous
Please show me something good
a good one
Here is the best one
This..
please leave me
Oh uncle, let go of what is holding you
Oh, who will leave me?
Please leave me, I will die
Leave me, save me..
Please leave.. Please leave uncle
- Save me
Why are you hitting me?
Please hit me?
- It's about to give up
let's go
Run.. Run
How did the door close?
Coming here.. What are you doing?
save me
- Opened
Run.. Run
Brother-in-law.. Brother-in-law
what happened
- A demon
a demon
How could your husband Ryan even think of this?
We will sell this palace for so low
Brother in law.. A demon is a demon
Yes, that's what I'm saying
Now there is not even a ghost in this palace
- This is a major property
It is so little.. only 8000 crores?
8000 crores?
did you see
What happened to the face of the little one.. that much less
Take your letter
- King, you are making a mistake
Says right
right?
Now.. get out
What have you done?
- This brother
brother in law
Manjulika's ghost has not left this palace
He tried to kill me even now.. Look
- What are you saying?
Is he the one who kicked him out?
- Where did you go?
He was also afraid of a demon and ran away..
- Yes, this is no Baba
He is the right king
I have not really had any rebirth
Do not leave demons and ghosts.. even if a mouse comes
He goes in his pants from time to time.. King
You don't understand
King.. where did you go?
Someone comes with a tape
King.. it is in pieces
Pahara, I will tear you to pieces
father
- Brother-in-law
Dad..
- Oh, my lord
Savitri also made a noise.. You are a thief
Follow me, king
First think how to escape from Manjulika
Grandpa.. Grandpa is saying..
Leave this castle and run away?
- No
Why.. home
- Fruit
I can't live on two scraps now, please
Even if Manjulika ate us..
But without selling this palace, we..
Then let's sell it
Who do you sell to?
- Arya is there
Rani Sahiba Mandira
He doesn't know anything about these demonic things
I touched you.. you touch him
Let's sell this palace to him
to the skin
Mrs. Mandira
Showed you the palace.. took you around the village
Showed the shopping mall.. How much more time will it take?
Take the palace and finish it
- I really liked the palace
That's why I prepared all the documents together with my lawyer
What are you saying?
- But I am
1000 crore will be given
Come on..
- Okay brother
Oh, it's a little less, let's do something
We don't even have time
- It's okay
The palace was yours
Let's go and pack
- But I have a small condition
what now
- I will take this palace after two days
On Durghashtmi day
- Oh... after two days?
It's getting too late.. No, you should take it now
- It was a very good day
Sorry..no deal before that
oh god
- Then the deal
do it with me
brother in law
- This is Vicki Kanna
Yes..a very big businessman
He is a very big man
Do you know how to greet?
- pee?
Then you make an offer
- Your Majesty
I love this property
So I trust you to pay dearly
Very much..
- 1000 crores will be given
I will give it now
do you give
He does the deal in two days
i will do it today
- What are you saying?
Please come then.. come inside
Wow.. what a great looking chair?
A great design
I love it
- This is valuable
This was the king's throne
Load the rest of the things into my car.. and I think it will be beautiful..
at home
This throne is a symbol of this palace
It is part of heritage
Madam.. I will take the palace
And everything here is mine.. I will do anything
The other.. who is he?
This is Mallika sir..
This palace is being restored
Now you don't need anything.. because I have this palace
Don't want to restore.. I want to design it again
And this is not the king's palace
There is my bar
bye
Please take it slowly.. take it carefully
- Then, Your Majesty
I will say goodbye to you
This palace is mine from tomorrow..
- Pranam
Mallika
Mallika how did this throne come back here?
I ask you something
And why are you sitting there?
- Kutawahapiya Para Balli
Shakchuni
Brainless wolves
Did you give him my throne?
Where did you get the strength?
How many times will it be taken away from me?
This is my throne
And if someone tries to touch it..
I will tear them to pieces and drink their blood
This is my throne
Dad.. Dad
Mallika.. inside..
- Say yes Mira
You are here?.. but your hand..
- Where?
I am here
Meera listen to me.. you know he is dead
who
- Vicky is dead
dead
I'm sorry
It's very harsh
Take it here.. it's dead
I thought he couldn't take your palace
So I will sign it two or three times
On Durghashtmi day
dead
Who laughs at the news of someone's death?
This seems strange to me
I feel a little weird too
I want to show the doctor
Ever since he arrived, something has been strange
I think the same
I doubt it..
- She is also called Manjulika
yes
Do you remember how you freaked out when you told the story of going to the mansion?
I don't believe in God
But the deal in the palace is also done on Durghashtmi day
Who are you talking about?
About mansions
Oh, I'm talking about Mallika
Oh, why do you doubt that helplessly?
He calls me his own brother
- That's it
How much more big hint will he give?
You don't know how angry he was looking at Vicky Kanna that day.. He talked to take the throne.
Oh man, Mandira was the one who was shaking in anger that day
When he took the deal in his palace from him
You don't even believe the story of me lifting the throne?
- Oh, how do you believe?
Mallika was with me then
- Don't believe it
But Mallika is Manjulika
I say
Mandira is Manjulika
what happened
This is what you think
Which of the two of us is Manjulika?
I am Manjulika
survived
There.. there
Forgive me God.. from today all wrong work will stop
Dad took her on a date for money
Again, I do not do demonic things
Where did I come?
Pandit.. The mall in this palace has become very dangerous
what happened
I saw a vampire on the roof yesterday
hey seriously
The cloth was opened
- That's me
Oh, how many times have you told me not to do that with long hair?
There are no demons, ghosts or ghouls
That's how it is
If Manjulika was there, I would be like that..
Humiliate him by telling him to embrace him
Will not be fine
- So how did Vicki Kanna die?
Nonsense
Where did Vicki Kanna die?
Athana is sitting on the settee in front of her.. Athana
Oh God.. talking about you
Where have you been?
- Serve sir
And when you sit on the throne
The three of us will take care of everything for you, sir
I will serve like that
The way you won't be found even in heaven after death
- Yes, nowhere else
Stretch your arms a little and throw 20 to 25 lakhs on your face
If you serve like this, you will definitely be beaten.
right sir
Do you know little Pandit?
Big men's hands
Much longer than the law
Doesn't this arm look too long?
Here the tension around the neck has increased
Would you mind giving me a little massage?
Gentlemen.. did you sit facing the other side?
oh god
Vicky G
You were a very good person
But we are the king's servants, right?
You only get to eat once in two days.. but do you even know if there is salt or not?
And we cannot do the work that serves us, sir
Goodbye.. Nice to meet you..
Hey hey leaving
- A demonic spirit
Hey leaving
leaving
Talking to avoid
No, no, sister
No no..
- Let's escape
What does Netflix turn on?
Sings a Bengali song
Listen.. did you sleep in my room last night?
No so?
No .. you got up and laughed then fell asleep
Did you laugh?
Is that so?
I will come.. he said not
He didn't accept.. I came suspecting him
Ghostbusters
- Take us out
please listen
Death has come here.. Their songs will never end
Dance, you thieves.. I'm going
Ruhan.. where are you going?
What happened? Why don't you say anything?
Oh, Ruhan, our marriage is going to happen
You... come up
the fruit
father
Father Ruhan left us all
Good job.. Good job
At least Manjulika did a good job by killing him
Oh, not dead.. He left the palace
It's very good for you.. I didn't like that boy at all from the beginning
Is there someone.. someone who is going to die.. someone who is going to die
What are you looking at?
If he dies, you will be guilty.. Pick it up and put it inside
please
What happened brother?
Oh, nothing.. I wanted to say
you..
What's going on?
Oh bro, who are you waiting for? Why don't you leave here?
Can't get out of this maze
Can't go.. Can't go
Hey escape little Pandit.. Death is also seen in your horoscope today
you
You left, didn't you?
- Can't go
can't go
leave you
Leave all of you
Now all of you are my family
When it's yours
- Our daughter has found a hero type boy
look
Let's eat
- Yes, let's go
shut up
Meera.. don't talk to me
With whom?
- Do with me.. Why did you come back here?
No one is saved here
Anyone becomes Manjulika.. we go
Can you go?
Because God has given you legs that you can't walk
- We also have our Rolls Royce
let's escape
- Good
See you in a while
What are these thieves doing? Let's go
Put this on
What are these.. Why?
Oh, Manjulika's gaze has fallen on us
If you wear these, you won't be able to catch them.. Cover your face
Can't see anything
Cover completely
Did you check everything?
He came back to where he was
Why did you bring it back to where you were, idiots?
I didn't bring it
Leave it..
- Rolls Royce
Oops
The vehicle split into two pieces
Take off the glasses
the hair
It is said that there is death in your horoscope today
The thief was killed
- Save, Mother Durga
This is the pure oil
With these you will finish the manjulika
But who is he?
Not the rebirth of the prince
Do you know what to do in the city?
They are deceiving people by pretending to drive out Bhutayon
do you know
I knew his truth on the first day
And I know this too
That the prophecies of my ancestors can never be wrong
Well, let's accept that I am the reincarnation of the prince
But who will put the oil?
Mandira or Mallika?
what
- Does that mean?
Do you think either of them is Manjulika?
Strange things have been happening since those two came here
Folard Singh.. You must have lived for such a long time with Manjulika in your lap.
Tell me who is Manjulika
- It's a very old incident, I don't remember Panditji
I will say.. I found the picture of Manjulika
Your younger brother dropped the ink on it
I sent it to the city to be cleaned
The crazy girl could have given us all of us doing the work beautifully
Oh, silly pumpkin, the ink is not cleaned with soap, but with a special chemical
Only one day left
Everything will be known tomorrow
- Tomorrow?
That means Durghashtmi day
Oh, we can only chase away false demons by pulling Baba's clothes
Manjulika is a vampire
- You don't understand
There is the oil
Then only oil can save us
- Please go and find out whether the picture has been cleaned or not
What are you two doing?
- Ghostbusters
I have had lice since childhood
The lice died, the mother died.. but the lice did not die
What oil did you use, sister?
- Kana Baba's Ayurvedic Oil
The company closed but the lice did not die
So we thought that if the demons were killed by this oil, our lice would also be killed
Does pure oil kill lice?
- Lucky you
No hair
- The hair?
Oh, that hair.. Podi Pandit
Or your hair will run out of oil
I will finish you both
- What are you doing? Oh, what kind of donkey are you?
Are you trying to beat yourself up with your own sandal?
Manjulika.. Manjulika
- Cheating rogue
Meera.. Meera
What are you doing Meera?
I had a very bad dream
I noticed
I burn myself alive
what
Meera
Give me the lighter
You were just as scared
Meera.. if anything happens to you
Then let's die together
yes
Let's burn together
I'm coming
come on
coming
Meera.. Meera
- Giving up.. Giving up
what happened to you
I.. I..
Was sitting with Mandira
i..
Mansions
Ruhan
- What's the problem?
What happened Ruhan?
- You have a fight with me
Why was Mira taken in the middle?
Meera
I didn't understand anything
- Stop this nadagama of yours
Were you waiting for Durghashtmee?
Today is Durghashtmee.. Either you finish me or I will finish you
Where.. start.. start
- What are you doing, are you crazy?
Ruhan
Don't get in the middle
Ruhan.. is taking
- The picture is clean
I am Manjulika
leaving me
- Give up?
Here.. gave up
I will kill my beloved brother first.. then you
What are you looking at my dear brother?
I'm coming.. I'm coming
my treasure
does it hurt
Here.. I will end your pain
- Ruhan
I'm going to kill you
are you ok
- Yes
please
Mrs. Mandira.. I'm sorry
I thought wrong about you.. are you ok?
I am very well now
You burned the wrong sister
save
I am Manjulika
This is my throne
my
save
This is how I shouted
And everyone was standing and watching Nadagama.. You are the ones who are shouting today
And I watch Nadagama
Manjulika.. with what strength can you be so arrogant?
Today is your end
Raja Purohita
did you see
Why is he turning to us now?
Paharayo gives his full attention to our family
do something
Miss Manjulika
Don't come near us.. Look at the sacred oil in our hair
You ask this Ghostbuster
He is the one who gave us the oil.. Tell me
I didn't give it. You two stole the oil.. Thieves
Pholard Singh.. protect us
Run away, who will protect me?
Oh Baba... Oh Baba
God protect us all
Chauhan
- Bang
Not Chauhan
Jawan (soldier)
the soldier
- Soldier?
Jawan ji took a big jump.. now you too can save us
Nadkin Paharaya.. How is he a soldier?
Can't get up even with help
the hair
Oh, this is not our thief Konda.. Podi Pandit
what are you saying
Podi Pandit too
- Podi Pandit.. What Podi Pandit?
Oh, his memory is gone
- Memory?
what is that
He takes the memory
Mallika G.. Mallika G
Do you remember?
Ruhan
I made a mistake
Don't do it to him
The secret I never knew my whole life
Faced with death
I remembered it in a moment
It's true
I am not a demon and he is not a demon
The time has come
Come forward and show your truth
Manjulica
Not Manjulika
Raja Kumar Devendranath
Debu
Do you dance night after night in the palace?
No, sister.. Oh, no
Why lie?
We saw you
Oh, why are you afraid?
We won't tell anyone
And we are your sisters
yes sister
I dance too
Our Debu dances so beautifully, isn't it?
beautiful
I like to dance very much
I love art
I don't want to be a king
To be honest, I am lonely inside
Like you guys
I am not Devendranath
I am Manjulika
Well then.. today we will decorate you
You dance.. then we sing
Ask my dear..
The melody of my love..
<font color="
flows through the atmosphere..
You gave him the throne because God was a man
Go and see how low he is
Innocently.. simply.. I was childish..
About the cunning tricks of the people of the world..
I didn't know..
So injured my innocent heart..
<font color="
These ties that have fallen from the string are the pearls..
After being lost, it will not be reunited..
My own loved ones have betrayed me in poisonous dreams..
Your Majesty.. What is the punishment to be given to him?
Death penalty
But what do you say to the people?
Announce to the whole kingdom that Rajakumara Devendranath has been killed
And his murder
That Manjulika did it
me
You two could have told this story even if I was alone
But you played this song in front of everyone for the sake of the throne
He danced that low dance for his brother
No son or daughter of mine
Not fit for this throne
From today you
He is known as the murderer of his brother
Then you are Anjulica
Your name will forever be erased from the pages of history
I will give both of you the punishment of exile from the country
<font color="
There was one house..
The house I thought was heaven turned into hell..
This body of mine was incomplete..
There was one house..
The house I thought was heaven turned into hell..
<font color="
No one is left alive.. Everyone is erased..
This body is finished.. This soul is not dead..
This soul is not afraid of any kind of tormentor..
This is Bhairav ​​Kavach
I knock at the door of Rajakumari Manjulika's room
Show people
Manjulika's soul is trapped there
No one wants to know that the soul is not really Manjulika's
That of Rajakumara Devendranath
And he is imprisoned here
I was stuck in that door for years
A fire burned to take revenge on both of you
When I came out, you two were in front of me
I wanted to kill both of you the first night
kill it
Then I thought
It is an easy and quick death for you
That you also want to be killed that way
Like it killed me
Burned alive
You two played with me last time
This time it's me
Little by little I gained everyone's trust
It's you two
called Manjulika
I said that I will not go to the mansion
I am Manjulika
Today before Durghashtmi day everyone..
You are on fire
then you
It can't be
No problem
Everyone will burn to death
Everyone burns alive
Rajapurohita
What is this?
Now how to save the royal family?
Think this first
How do you survive?
Look below
Where are you standing at this time?
Said to go.. going.. going far away
Said to go
Burn him
Rebirth is not Ruhan's
It happened to both of you
Cook and grind
- Run away
Said to go far.
Run away
Said to go
I trust you both, sister
Who else understands me like sisters?
I love you both so much
Our rebirth is not to repeat our mistakes
It has to be fixed
If you are burned, we are also about you (jealousy).
But because of our soul..
Everyone burned you brutally
You were always stuck..
While living in a human body
Then after death
Behind that door
We couldn't understand you
We are sorry brother
Sorry Deboo
If your revenge is complete by punishing us..
Then kill us.. burn us
But let them go
There is nothing wrong with them
What's going on?
He gets immunity
My ancestors were right
Someone from the royal family will be reborn to finish him off
And I couldn't understand.. that end
<font color="
that you will understand
{\an2\candH00F5F8
Visit www.PirateLk.Com for Sinhala subtitles
..100th subtitle..
I have seen this palace since childhood
I knew
With this place for me..
There must be some connection
So I started restoring old palaces
I thought.. who knows
If you ever get to know anything about this palace
But when there is an opportunity
The company handed over my place to Kaushik ji
So.. that's why you are Kaushik ji
Why am I killing him?
But you said he went on a long vacation
He went on a really long vacation.. Goa
oh
I also came here for another job
But when you come here
I also felt something
That means you didn't come to take this palace, Mr. Mandira?
My name is not even Mandira
then?
ACP Rathore
ACP Rathore?
- Yes
Madhuri
{\an2\candH00F5F8
Visit www.PirateLk.Com for Sinhala subtitles